vailresorts.com 2001-06-04

# Snow.com | Vail Beaver Creek Breckenridge Keystone - Legal

> **Vail Resorts Management Company Internet Privacy Policy**
> 
> UPDATED 09/05/2000
> 
>   
>  The Vail Corporation and its subsidiary companies ("VRMC") are committed to protecting the personal privacy of visitors and guests using its Internet sites. 
> 
> VRMC’s privacy policy aims to accomplish three basic goals: 
> 
>   * VRMC will not release personally identifiable information without consent.
>   * VRMC will allow the user to control certain aspects of the information voluntarily submitted.
>   * VRMC encourages its site users to communicate privacy concerns and VRMC will respond to such concerns.
> 
**Coverage**
> 
> This privacy policy applies to VRMC owned and operated sites. 
> 
> **Definitions of Types of Information**
> 
> Personally identifiable information is information or other data that may specifically identify an individual user. In order for you to access certain services and to purchase services that we offer via the Sites, we require you to provide us with such Personal Information. Personal Information may include: (i) Contact Data (such as your name, mailing and e-mail addresses); (ii) Financial Data (such as your account or credit card number); and (iii) Demographic Data (such as your zip code, age and income). If you communicate with us by e-mail or otherwise complete online forms, surveys or contest entries, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information. 
> 
> Traffic Data shall not be considered personally identifiable information or Personal Information. Traffic Data is information on a user’s patterns of access and usage of the sites. We automatically track and collect the following information when you visit our Site, including your: (i) IP address; (ii) domain server; (iii) type of computer; and (iv) type of web browser. Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify you but is helpful for marketing purposes or for improving your experience on the Site. We also use "cookies" to as a method to gain dependable and consistant Traffic Data. "Cookies" are anonymous and do not personally identify you. 
> 
> **Collection and Use of Personally Identifiable Information**
> 
> Registration 
> 
> A user may access and utilize the vast majority of VRMC site functionality without transmitting any Personal Information. In order to access certain other functionality, VRMC may request the user provide personally identifiable information. At no time is the user under any obligation to provide Personal Information. If the user does not wish to access such functionality, the user should not transmit the personally identifiable information. 
> 
> During the registration process VRMC shall require the user to complete certain data fields. Some fields may be optional. VRMC shall request contact information and shall utilize such information in the following manner: 
> 
>   * to send communications regarding the Vail Resorts.
>   * to share user information with specific strategic partners, if and only if authorized to do so by the user.
>   * to allow specific strategic partners to communicate with the user, if and only if authorized to do so by the user.
> 
If you indicate to us that you do not want to receive certain types of communications at the time of registration, we will respect your wishes, and comply with your preferences. If you already are a registered user and would like to review or change the choices you have made, you may [click here](mailto:privacy-support@vailresorts.com) to email us at privacy-support@vailresorts.com for assistance. 
> 
> Contests, Etc. 
> 
> From time to time, we may run contests on our site in which we ask participants for contact information, such as their e-mail address(es). If you participate in contests, your contact information will be used primarily to reach you in connection with the contests. We may also use the collected contact information to send you information about Vail Resorts, our services, as well as offers tailored to your interests by our corporate partners, if you have opted to receive these communications. You may choose to opt-out of receiving such mailings at the time of registration for the contest, or afterwards, by [click here](mailto:privacy-support@vailresorts.com) to email us at privacy-support@vailresorts.com. 
> 
> **Sharing Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties**
> 
> In order to optimize and improve the online experience for our guests, we may share your Personal Information with carefully selected companies with whom we have relationships. However, we will not share your personally identifiable information unless you have given us your consent to do so, as in our registration forms. If you have previously opted-in, but now wish to remove yourself from these mailing lists, you may send email directly to [privacy-support@vailresorts.com](mailto:privacy-support@vailresorts.com), and we will modify your preference accordingly. Our partners who receive information from us have the right to use the data we provide them (sometimes, in connection with other information they may have gathered about you). 
> 
> **PLEASE NOTE:** In certain special cases, we may disclose your personally identifiable information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to you, or otherwise injuring or interfering with VRMC's rights, property or operations, other VRMC site users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We may also disclose your personally identifiable information when we believe the law requires it, or in response to any demand by law enforcement authorities in connection with a criminal investigation, or civil or administrative authorities in connection with a pending civil case, administrative investigation or investigation conducted by VRMC. We shall have no obligation to inform you of our compliance with the law, including without limitation a response to a law enforcement request or a valid subpoena. 
> 
> **Traffic Data**
> 
> When you use our site, we collect Traffic Data, even if you have not registered with VRMC. We use this information to personalize your experience at all the sites that VRMC operates and generally to improve our services. We share this Traffic Data with selected corporate partners. 
> 
> **Cookies: How They Are Used**
> 
> How They Are Used 
> 
> A "cookie" is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies do not damage your system or impair its functioning in any way. We use cookies to help us provide customizable services and to allow you to sign-in to our site. Cookies may also be used by VRMC corporate partners on co-branded Web pages, as explained below in "third party relationships," so please be aware of this as you visit these Web pages. 
> 
> You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features will not work as intended. 
> 
> **Children/Family Filter**
> 
> VRMC is concerned about protecting the safety of the children who use our site. The VRMC sites – sites directed to a broad, general audience – comply with the terms of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. As such, we will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information on users under the age of 13,without the consent of a parent to do so. Parents have the ability to control what, if any, Personal Information about their child may be disclosed to third parties, by regulating the actions and behavior of their children using the internet. 
> 
> **Use of IP Addresses**
> 
> An Internet protocol (IP) address is a set of numbers that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you log on to your internet service provider or through your company’s local area network (LAN) or wide area network (WAN). Web servers - the powerful computers that provide web pages for viewing - automatically identify your computer by the IP address assigned to it during your session online. 
> 
> VRMC may collect IP addresses for purposes of system administration, to report user Traffic Data to our corporate partners (as explained above), and to audit the use of our site. We do not ordinarily link a user’s IP address to the Personal Information of that user, which means each user’s session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us. However, we can and will use IP addresses to identify users of our site when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our site’s Terms and Conditions of Use or terms of service, or to protect our service, site, or other users. 
> 
> **PLEASE NOTE:** Under certain circumstances, IP addresses and/or domain names may be linked to personally identifiable information, when said information is stored in databases managed by Internet registrars or registries such as [Network Solutions](http://www.networksolutions.com/). 
> 
> **Third-Party Relationships**
> 
> In order to optimize your experience on our sites, VRMC maintains relationships with many corporate partners and service providers throughout the world. If you have any questions about whether certain information, content or services pertain to us, or are provided by one of our partners, please contact us at [privacy-support@vailresorts.com](mailto:privacy-support@vailresorts.com). 
> 
> Whenever you provide registration information on certain Web pages or for certain services provided in conjunction with third party partners, we want to be clear that some data you provide is shared with partners. For instance, certain information is shared with WorldRes.com, our provider of online reservation service. You should make every effort to read the privacy policies provided by or in association with such third parties, and make an informed decision on your own whether or not to continue utilizing the services based upon the privacy policies posted on these Web pages, at your own discretion. However, we will make every effort to ensure that you have the ability to opt-out of the sharing of such data with partners. You may email us directly at [privacy-support@vailresorts.com](mailto:privacy-support@vailresorts.com) and we will forward your request to the appropriate company, and help you follow up to ensure that your concerns are adequately handled. 
> 
> In addition to finding these Web pages, you will find direct links on VRMC to the sites offered by third parties. Some of these sites are authorized to use the Vail Resorts brands and/or logos. VRMC carefully evaluates all parties that are authorized to use its brands and/or logos, and believes that all such sites have adopted acceptable privacy policies. Again, you should read these third party privacy policies, and make an informed decision on your own as to whether or not to continue based upon these sites' privacy practices, at your own discretion. No third-party sites are covered by this Privacy Policy. 
> 
> **VERY IMPORTANT:** If you feel that a site using the VRMC brands and/or logos has not posted an acceptable privacy policy, or is not following the privacy policy it has posted, please send us an email at [privacy-support@vailresorts.com](mailto:privacy-support@vailresorts.com). If appropriate, we may forward complaints to the appropriate third parties and help you follow up to ensure that your concerns are adequately handled. Of course, if any of these third party companies does not have a privacy policy that is acceptable to you, you should refrain from providing information until your concerns have been satisfactorily addressed. 
> 
> **Security**
> 
> VRMC operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection. VRMC has security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your user data under our control. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration to data will not occur, we make every reasonable effort to prevent such unfortunate occurrences. 
> 
> You must promptly notify us if your credit card, pass product with ResortCharge, user name or password is lost, stolen or used without permission. In such an event, we will cancel that credit card number, pass product, user name or password and update our records accordingly. 
> 
> **Contacting Us**
> 
> If you have questions about this privacy policy or the practices of this site, please contact: 
> 
> Office of the General Counsel  
>  Vail Resorts, Inc.  
>  Box 7, Legal 88  
>  Vail, CO 81658 
> 
> You can send email to [privacy-support@vailresorts.com](mailto:privacy-support@vailresorts.com). 
> 
> VRMC reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. All changes will be posted to this page, and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to notify you of any significant changes to this privacy policy. However, it is your responsibility to check this site for any such updates as you will be bound by them should you choose to visit our sites.
